

Garin McCullick

573-680-8460

glmccullick@gmail.com

SUMMARY

User-minded Web Developer prioritizes usability and adaptability during all projects. Designs sites and apps to attract users with aesthetically pleasing interfaces and exceptional UX elements. Comfortable working within large-scale collaborations or on individually-developed assets, with experience working on team based applications.

SKILLS

- Html5
- Css3
- JavaScript
- React

- Redux
- Git
- Npm

EXPERIENCE

Setup Specialist

Springfield, MO

SRC Holdings Corp/Jan 2022 to Current

- Received deliveries, scanned packages and updated orders in internal database.
- Operated forklifts to fill or empty overhead spaces.
- Identified defective, incorrect or missing merchandise and promptly corrected them inside our database.

Web Developer

Freelance Jan 2020 to Current

- Redesigned sites to enhance navigation and improve visual appeal.
- Created, tested, and implemented user authentication on multiple web applications.
- Collaborated with UI and UX personnel to develop friendly and usable websites and web-based software.
- Contributed back-end development experience and collaborated on multiple APIs crucial to functionality.

Construction Worker

El Dorado Springs, MO

McCullick & Sons Construction/ Aug 2016 to Jan 2022

- Completed carpentry work, including installing crown molding and wood flooring to meet customer preferences.
- Performed skilled and semi-skilled repairs to existing roofs, including shingle replacement.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development

Lambda School

Silicon Valley, California

Feb 2021 - June 2021

Some College (No Degree): Computer Application Development

State Technical College of Missouri

Linn, MO

Jan 2020 - May 2020

CONTACT

- https://www.garin-mccullick.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/garin-mccullick-891a2320a/
- https://github.com/GarinMcCullick